steelband.co.uk 2019-12-13

# PRIVACY POLICY | Steelasophical Caribbean Music

Skip to content

PRIVACY POLICY[G a r y Trotman](https://steelband.co.uk/author/steebandcouk/ "Posts by G a r y Trotman")2019-06-10T18:49:58+01:00

> If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this site, please contact me.

## **General:**

I care about providing you with tools and information to manage and protect your online privacy. I have developed this privacy policy to inform you about what information this web site collects, who may receive that information, what I may do with the information, and how long it is kept. While I have made every attempt to make this policy as clear as possible, if you have any further questions about it, feel free to contact me.

### **Your Information:**

I will not give out any information you submit at this site to any third parties except in compliance with a request of a law enforcement agency. Under no circumstances will your name, e-mail, phone number or address be sold to, or given to any other parties. I will never wilfully sell, lease, or rent any of your or your business’ personally identifiable information to any third party.

### **Collected Information:**

Your personal information is collected through the contact forms only. This website currently has no applications or programs that gather information from your computer without your consent. Users are required to give contact information (e.g., your name and email address) and demographic information (e.g., your postcode). Certain information, such as your email address, is collected in order to verify your identity and for use in my records. Information collected at this website is kept in my records only as long as is necessary to provide requested services to my clients.

### **Summation:**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this site, please contact me.

## PRIVACY POLICY

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails
  * The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.  
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorised with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.  
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognise your browser and capture and remember certain information.  
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and understand and save your preferences for future visits.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

2020
